[left hand] grasp the blue block | [right hand] grasp the green block | [ego] stay still
[left hand] place the blue block on the green block | [right hand] place the red block on the green block | [ego] stay still
[left hand] grasp the purple block | [right hand] grasp the green block | [ego] stay still
[left hand] place the purple block on the blue block | [right hand] place the green block on the red block | [ego] stay still
[left hand] grasp the green block | [right hand] grasp the red block | [ego] stay still
[left hand] place the green block on the purple block | [right hand] place the red block on the green block | [ego] stay still
[left hand] grasp the purple block | [right hand] grasp the yellow block | [ego] stay still
[left hand] place the purple block on the green block | [right hand] place the yellow block on the red block | [ego] stay still
[left hand] grasp the green block | [right hand] grasp the blue block | [ego] stay still
[left hand] place the green block on the yellow block | [right hand] place the blue block on the green block | [ego] stay still
[left hand] grasp the yellow block | [right hand] grasp the green block | [ego] stay still
[left hand] place the yellow block on the blue block | [right hand] place the green block on the yellow block | [ego] stay still
[left hand] grasp the blue block | [right hand] grasp the yellow block | [ego] stay still
[left hand] place the blue block on the green block | [right hand] place the yellow block on the blue block | [ego] stay still